A Guide to the Papers of Archie G. Richardson 1918-1976
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Photographs and Negatives
  - African American Schools in Virginia
    - Norfolk County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:46)
      - Churchland School 1932
      - Norfolk County Court House
      - South Hill School 1931-1932
    - Northumberland County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:47)
      - Mrs. Knentz and daughter
      - Faculty County Training School 1932-1933
      - Faculty Northumberland County Training School 1931-1932
      - Northumberland County White School
      - 3rd grade Northumberland 1931-1932
      - 11th grade Northumberland County Training School 1931-1932
      - Mila School Northumberland County
      - Northumberland County Court House (6)
      - 11th grade Northumberland County Training School 1932-1933
      - Supt. Frank W. Lewis
      - Home of Mr.Krentz (2)
    - Northampton County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:48)
      - Maids of Honor of County Queen 1933
      - Queen of Thrown 1933
      - Tidewater Senior Class (2) 1935-1936
      - Northampton County
      - H.S. Northampton County (Cape Charles) 1934-1935
      - Gearge Aliner Jr.
      - Trustees of Tidewater Institute 1930-1931
      - Northampton County Field Day Exercises 1933
      - 8th grade Cape Charles School 1932-1933
      - Student Body Cape Charles School 1932-1933
      - Teachers of Cape Charles School 1932-1933
      - Supt. G.J.Aliner (3)
      - Supt D.W.Pilers
      - Northampton County Court House
      - Lucy Evans Akkinson (2) 1934
      - Massawaddox School
    - Nottoway County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:49)
      - Sneads Spring School (2)
      - Prospect School
      - Fergusonville School 1935
      - Nottoway County Training School Senior Class 1934-1935
      - 11th grade Nottoway County Training School 1933
      - Home Economics House Nottoway County Training School 1933
      - Jennings School
      - Hickory grove
      - Burkeville School
      - Watson School
      - Dr. and Mrs. Atler Ingleside Seminary
    - Orange County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:50)
      - Ridge School
      - Isabella Lightfoot 1935
      - Orange County Training School H.S. Group 1932-1933
      - Orange County Training School H.S. Group 8th and 9th 1932-1933
      - Orange County Training School
      - Nason School
      - Orange County Enhance Day 1935
      - Orange County School Exhibit Day (2) 1935
      - Orange County (2)
      - Senior Class Orange County Training School 1934-1935
      - Faculty Orange County Training School 1934-1935
      - School Number 17 Barbersville
      - Manrae Wood School
      - 11th grade Orange County Training School 1933-1934
      - Orange County Court House
      - Hunting Group Jan 1935
      - Za School
      - Chorus Class 1934-1935
    - Page County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:51)
      - Salem School 1932-1933
      - 8th and 9th grades Luney School
      - Blainesville School 1932-1933
      - Walker Creek School (2) 1932-1933
      - Blainesville School Children 1932-1933
      - Walkers Creek School 1932-1933
      - Luney School 1932-1933
      - Page County Court House
    - Patrick County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:52)
      - Patrick County
      - West Liberty School 1932
      - Cross Roads School
      - New Lake School
      - West Liberty Children 1932
      - Colored School and Church
      - Willis Gap School 1932
      - Rev Hallow School
      - Rev Hallow School Children (2) 1932-1933
      - Harden Reynolds School
      - Supt.Clifton 1932
      - Patrick County Court House
      - Children of Weeping Willow School 1932
      - Willis Gap School
      - New Hife School Children 1932
    - Pittsylvania County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:53)
      - Henry school
      - Whitemell (white) School
      - Gretna White School
      - Faculty of Pittsylvania Coutny Court House 1930-1931
      - Pittsylvania County Training School Faculty Our Teacher failed to get in 1931-1932
      - 11th grade Gretna School (2) 1933-1934
      - Glass School
      - 11th grade Pittsylvania County Training School 1931-1932
      - Pupils of Ramsey School 1931-1932
      - Camp Grove School
      - Pittsylvania County
      - Ajax School Children 1932
      - Dixie School
      - 11th grade Gretna School 1931-1932
      - Jaytonsville School
      - 11th grade Pittsylvania County Training School 1930-1931
      - Old Building Shields School Sept 24
      - Antioch School
      - Muller School
      - Supt. Nelson and Officer Force
      - Crookstown School
      - Supt J.B. Watson Jr.
      - PIttsylvania County Court House
    - Powhatan County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 22:54)
      - Corinth School 1933-1934
      - C.F. Simpson and Family 1932
      - Group of children Powhatan County Training School 1931-1932
      - Group at Powhatan County Training School 1931-1932
      - Mrs. Simpson and Mrs.Allen Logansville School 1931-1932
      - Faculty County Training School 1933-1934
      - Donsel School 1933-1934
      - Powhatan County Training School 11th grade 1934-1935
      - Antioch School 1935
      - Ballsville School 1932-1933
      - Primary Grade Powhatan County Training School
      - 7th grade Powhatan County Training School 1932-1933
      - Logansville School
      - Wilkerson School
      - 10th and 11th grade Powhatan County Training School
      - Powhatan County Teachers 1932-1933
      - Fine Creek School 1933-1934
      - Shiloh School 1934
      - New Powhatan White School 1931-1932
      - Supt. P.C. Williams
      - Powhatan County Court House (2)
      - Pilkington School
    - Prince Edward County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:1-3)
      - Peak School 1934
      - Homw of T.J. McHarvoni Farmville,Va
      - 11th grade Prince Edward County Training School 1934-1935
      - 11th grade Prince Edward County Training School 1931-1932
      - Froward Rack School 1934
      - High Bridge School 1934
      - Sulphier Springs School 1934
      - 11th grade Prince Edward County Training School 1932-1933
      - 11th grade prince Edward County Training School 1933-1934
      - Ms. Moveah School 1934
      - Prospus School Number 2 1934
      - High Ranks School 1934
      - Beam School
      - Epps School 1934
    - Prince George County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:4)
      - Faculty Prince George Training School 1932-1933
      - Darnell Bricks County
      - New County White School Building 1935
      - Prince George County Reeves School number 5
      - Prince George County Teachers 1931-1932
      - Prince George County Training School 1934
      - View of Exhibit Day Prince George County Training School 1932
    - Princess Anne County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:5)
      - Princess Anne County Teachers 1932-1933
      - Broad Creek School
      - Union Kempsville School 1933-1934
      - Furman School Buildings
      - Princess Anne County Court Court House
      - Old Home
      - Suph Cornell and Family
      - William Frank Hotel
      - William Frank Hotel 1935
      - St.Johns School
      - Mac Penson School
    - Prince William County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:6)
      - Mantico School
      - Thorofare School
      - Summit School
      - Mt.Zion School (Church)
      - Antioch School Children
      - Kettle Run School
      - 7th grade Graduates Brown School
    - Pulaski County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:7)
      - Pulasi County Court House
      - Supt. E.L. Darsh
    - Rappahannock County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:8)
      - Colored School Washington VA Exhibit Day 1931
      - Group of Little Washington (2) May 1932
      - The Rudesill Girls-Mandeville 1935
      - Supt. G. Tyler Miller
      - Rappahannock County Court House (2)
      - Peola Mills School 1932-1933
      - Rappahannock and Warren County Negro Teachers 1932-1933
      - Colored School-Exhibit Day 1931
    - Richmond County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:9)
      - Senior Class Academy School 1934-1935
      - Mayfield School 1935
      - 11th grade No Neck Academy 1930-1931
      - Ebernizer School 1935
      - Ms. Julia Pope and R.D. Pope 1930-1931
      - Faculty No Neck Academy 1930-1931
      - Mrs. Julia Pope 1931
      - Dawnings School (2) 1935
      - Richmond County Court House (2)
      - Richmond County Clerks Office
    - Roanoke County 1930-1934 (Box-folder 23:10)
      - Roanoke County Court House
      - Roanoke County Training School Faculty 1931-1932
      - H.S. Dept Roanoke County Training School 1930-1931
      - Roanoke County Training School Faculty 1932
      - 10th grade Roanoke County Training School 1933-1934
      - H.S. Dept Roanoke County Training School 1932-1933
    - Rockbridge County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:11)
      - 9th grade Rockbridge County Training School 1932-1933
      - Brawnsbury School Children 1932-1933
    - Rickingham County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:12)
      - Waltner School 1934
      - McGaheysville School 1934
      - Bridgeway School 1934
      - Miss Laurie Walker and Teacher Waltner School 1934
      - Supt. Indy and Principal H. Waddell
      - Supt. Myers
      - Rockingham County Court House
    - Scott County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:13)
      - Scott County Court House
      - Supt. Smith
    - Shenandoah County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:14)
      - Ms. Jackson School
      - Shenandoah County Court House
    - Smyth County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:15)
      - Principal Epps Mirror School 1931-1932
      - H.S. Group Marian School 1931-1932
      - Smyth County Court House (2)
      - Supt. Crougey
    - Southampton County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:16)
      - Dayle School 1935
      - New Franklin School
      - 11th grade Southampton County Training School 1930-1931
      - Supt. B.T. Watkins 1931
      - Sunbeam School 1935
      - Delaware School 1935
      - Ricks School 1935
      - Diamond Grove School 1935
      - 11th grade Southampton County Training School 1934-1935
      - 11th grade Southampton County Training School 1931-1932
      - Mrs. Brauns Home Eco Class County Training School 1931-1932
      - Southampton County School (2)
      - Mrs. Hill School (Mt. Olive) 1935
      - Sealy School 1935
      - Capron School
      - Southampton County Court House
      - Supt. J.J.Jenkins
      - Southampton County
      - Negro School
      - Southampton County Training School
      - Mrs. Winston and Mother
    - Spotsylvania County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:17)
      - Spotsylvania County School
      - Faculty Spotsylvania County Training School
      - Half Grade School 1933-1934
      - H.S. Dept County Training School 1932-1933
      - Massponax School 1933-1934
      - Spotsylvania County Training School 11th grade 1933-1934
      - Spotsylvania County Training School 1934
      - Fork School 1933-1934
      - Additional Rooms Spotsylvania County Training School 1934
      - Board Half School 1933-1934
      - Granite Springs School
      - Stubles School
      - Piney Branch School 1933-1934
      - Mayre School 1933-1934
      - Sunrise School
      - High School Group 1931-1932
      - State Negro Midwives
      - Supt. J.H.Charles
      - Faculty County Training School 1931-1932
      - Summit School 1932-1933
      - Good Hope School (2) 1933-1934
    - Stafford County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:18)
      - Falmouth School 1932
      - Falmouth School 1935
      - Union Branch School 1933-1934
      - Break School 1935
      - Oak Grove School 1935
      - Stafford County Teachers 1933-1934
      - Shiloh School 1933-1934
      - Little Forest School 1933-1934
      - Sherwood Taveil 1933
      - Stafford County School Board (2) 1933
      - Tommy Gayle
      - Stafford County Court House
      - Sherwood Forest School 1933
    - Surry County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:19)
      - Surry County Training School Faculty 1930-1931
      - 11th grade Surry County Training School
      - Spring Grove School
      - H.S. Dept Surry County Training School 1933-1934
      - 8th grade Surry County Training School 1930-1931
      - Gwen and Walter Jones
      - Faculty Surry County Training School 1933-1934
      - Poplarlawn School Children 1930-1931
      - New Design School 1934
      - Mt. Pleasent School
      - H.S. Dept Surry County Training School 1931-1932
      - Manassas Institution
      - Senior Class-Manassas Institution 1933-1934
    - Sussex County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:20)
      - Rivers School
      - Colored Teachers Sussex County 1931-1932
      - Surry County Court House Exercises 1931
      - H.S. Dept Sussex County Training School 1932-1933
      - Baker School 1935
      - Mrs. Jackson and Girls County Training School 1931
      - H.S. Students County Training School 1931-1932
      - H.S Dept County Training School 1932-1933
      - Hammerville School
    - Tazewell County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:21)
      - Tazewell School Teachers(2) 1931-1932
      - Pinnacle Rock
      - Patrons of Tazewell School 1930-1931
      - 8th grade Tazewell Grade School 1931-1932
      - Mud Fork School 1932-1933
      - Burkes Garden (white) School
      - Tazewell Graded School Teachers 1931-1932
      - Tazewell County Court House (2)
    - Warrick County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:22)
      - Lee Hall School
    - Warren County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:23)
      - New Front Royal School 1933
      - Pine Tree School
      - Beaver Damn School
      - Frank Royal School
      - Walklam School (Hanover County)
      - New Annion School
    - Washington County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:24)
      - Faculty Washington County Training School 1931-1932 (Box-folder 23:24)
      - H.S.Dept Washington County Training School 1931-1932
      - Washington County Court House
    - Westymoreland County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:25)
      - Faculty of Westmoreland County Training School 1931-1932
      - Zocata School (2) 1934
      - Hackett Hill School 1932
      - Kremlin School 1932
      - Zion School 1932
      - Residence of Supt. Blake T. Newton
      - Monroe Hall School 1935
      - George Washington School 1935
      - 11th grade Westmoreland County Training School 1933
      - Gravel Run School 1935
      - 8th grade Westmoreland County Training School 1931-1932
      - H.S. Dept Westmoreland County Training School 1932-1933
      - Supt. Blake T. Newton
      - Supt Blake T. Newton Oct. 22
    - Wise County 1928-1932 (Box-folder 23:26)
      - Negro School
      - 4th and 5th grade Wise County Training School 1931-1932
      - H.S. Students Wise County Training School 1931-1932
      - Quartet-Pine Ridge School 1932
      - Supt. J.J. Reely Jr.
      - Wise County Court House
      - Supt. Reely and Son May 1928
    - Wythe County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:27)
      - New Hope School Children 1931-1932
      - Wythe County Training School 1931-1932
      - Max Meadows School Children 1931-1932
      - H.S. Students Wyth County Training School 1932-1933
      - Austinville School Children 1931-1932
    - York County 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:28)
      - Oak Grove School
      - Yorktown (white) School
      - 11th grade York County Training School 1932-1933
      - Faculty-York County Training School 1932-1933
      - York County Training School -Home Economics Building
      - Tabb School
      - Senior Class York County Training School 1934-1935
      - York County Court House
    - Berryville,VA 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:29)
      - Supt. Richardson's 2 Children (2) 1934
    - Bluefield,VA 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:30)
      - Colored High School
      - Quartet at Bluefield VA 1931-1932
    - Bristol City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:31)
      - H.S. Dept Bristol City 1930-1931
      - Supt. R.C. Baners
      - Faculty Bristol City School 1930-1931
    - Emory City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:32)
      - Children of H.L. Crawgey 1934
    - Fredericksburg City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:33)
      - Teachers Fredericksburg Elementary School 1934-1935
    - Harrisonburg City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:34)
      - Graduating Class Harrisonburg Training School 1933
      - 11th grade Harrisonburg Training School 1934-1935
    - Hopewell City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:35)
      - 11th grade Hopewell School 1931-1932
      - Hopwell Teachers 1931-1932
      - Suot R.H.Wake
    - Lexington City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:37)
      - 11th grade Lexington School 1934-1935
      - Miss Virginia Randolph
      - School Bus
      - H.S. Group 8th and 9th grades
    - Lynchburg City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:38)
      - Dunbar High School (2)
    - Norfolk City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:40)
      - New School Building
    - Staunton City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:41)
      - Supt. F.L. Shelbourne
      - Senior Class Staunton High Scholl 1934-1935
    - Williamsburg City 1930-1935 (Box-folder 23:42)
      - Negro High School
    - Winchester 1930-1934 (Box-folder 23:44)
      - Faculty Colored School 1933-1934
      - Handly School 1934
    - R.R.Morton (Box-folder 21:46)
      - R.R. Morton at his home in Tidewater,VA
  - Negatives
    - Accomack County (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Accomack County (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Albermarle County (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Albermarle County (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Alleghany County (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Amelia County (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Amherst County (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Appomattox County (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Arlington County (Box-folder 24:9)
    - August County (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Bath County (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Bedford County (Box-folder 24:12)
    - Bland County (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Botetourt County (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Brunswick County (Box-folder 24:15)
    - Brunswick County (Box-folder 24:16)
    - Buchanan County (Box-folder 24:17)
    - Buckingham County (Box-folder 24:18)
    - Campbell County (Box-folder 24:19)
    - Campbell County (Box-folder 24:20)
    - Caroline County (Box-folder 24:21)
    - Carroll County (Box-folder 25:1)
    - Charles City County (Box-folder 25:2)
    - Charlotte County (Box-folder 25:3)
    - Chesterfield County (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Chesterfield County (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Chesterfield County (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Chesterfield County (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Clarke County (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Craig County (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Culpepper County (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Cumberland County (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Dinwiddie County (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Elizabeth City County (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Essex County (Box-folder 25:14)
    - Essex County (Box-folder 25:15)
    - Essex-Franklin County (Box-folder 25:16)
    - Faquier County (Box-folder 25:17)
    - Faquier County (Box-folder 25:18)
    - Fairfax County (Box-folder 25:19)
    - Fairfax County (Box-folder 25:20)
    - Floyd County (Box-folder 25:21)
    - Fluvanna County (Box-folder 25:22)
    - Fluvanna County (Box-folder 25:23)
    - Franklin County (Box-folder 25:24)
    - Franklin County (Box-folder 25:25)
    - Franklin County (Box-folder 25:26)
    - Frederick County (Box-folder 25:27)
    - Frederick County (Box-folder 25:28)
    - Giles County (Box-folder 25:29)
    - Gloucester County (Box-folder 25:30)
    - Gloucester County (Box-folder 25:31)
    - Goochland County (Box-folder 25:32)
    - Goochland County (Box-folder 25:33)
    - Grayson County (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Greene County (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Greensille County (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Greensville County (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Halifax County (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Halifax County (Box-folder 26:6)
    - Halifax County (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Halifax County (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Hanover County (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Henry County (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Henry County (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Highland County (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Isle of Wright County (Box-folder 26:13)
    - James City County (Box-folder 26:14)
    - King George County (Box-folder 26:15)
    - King George County (Box-folder 26:16)
    - King and Queen County (Box-folder 26:17)
    - King and Queen County (Box-folder 26:18)
    - King William County (Box-folder 26:19)
    - Lancaster County (Box-folder 26:20)
    - Lancaster County (Box-folder 26:21)
    - Loudon County (Box-folder 26:22)
    - Lee County (Box-folder 26:23)
    - Louisa County (Box-folder 26:24)
    - Lunenburg County (Box-folder 26:25)
    - Madison County (Box-folder 26:26)
    - Matthew County (Box-folder 26:27)
    - Macklenburg County (Box-folder 26:28)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box-folder 26:29)
    - Middlesex County (Box-folder 26:30)
    - Montgomery County (Box-folder 26:31)
    - Nansemond County (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Nensemond County (Box-folder 27:2)
    - Nelson County (Box-folder 27:3)
    - New Kent County (Box-folder 27:4)
    - New Kent County (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Norfolk County (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Norfolk County (Box-folder 27:7)
    - Northampton County (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Northampton County (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Northumberland County (Box-folder 27:10)
    - Northumberland County (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Nottoway County (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Nottoway County (Box-folder 27:13)
    - Orange County (Box-folder 27:14)
    - Page County (Box-folder 27:15)
    - Patrick County (Box-folder 27:16)
    - Pittsylvania County (Box-folder 27:17)
    - Pittsylvania County (Box-folder 27:18)
    - Prince Edward County (Box-folder 27:19)
    - Prince Edward County (Box-folder 27:20)
    - Prince George County (Box-folder 27:21)
    - Prince George County (Box-folder 27:22)
    - Prince William County (Box-folder 27:23)
    - Princess Anne County (Box-folder 27:24)
    - Powhatan County (Box-folder 27:25)
    - Pulaski County (Box-folder 27:26)
    - Rappahannock County (Box-folder 27:27)
    - Richmond County (Folder 27:28)
    - Roanoke County (Box-folder 27:29)
    - Roanoke County (Box-folder 28:30)
    - Rockingham County (Box-folder 27:31)
    - Rockingham County (Box-folder 27:32)
    - Russell County (Box-folder 27:33)
    - Russell County (Box-folder 27:34)
    - Scott County (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Shenandoah County (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Smyth County (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Southampton County (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Southampton County (Box-folder 28:5)
    - Spotsylvania County (Box-folder 28:6)
    - Stafford County (Box-folder 28:7)
    - Stafford County (Box-folder 28:8)
    - Surry County (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Sussex County (Box-folder 28:10)
    - Sussex County (Box-folder 28:11)
    - Tazewell County (Box-folder 28:12)
    - Tazewell County (Box-folder 28:13)
    - Warrick County (Box-folder 28:14)
    - Warren County (Box-folder 28:15)
    - Washington County (Box-folder 28:16)
    - Washington County (Box-folder 28:17)
    - Westmoreland County (Box-folder 28:18)
    - Westmoreland County (Box-folder 28:19)
    - Winchester County (Box-folder 28:20)
    - Wise County (Box-folder 28:21)
    - Wythe County (Box-folder 28:22)
    - Wythe County (Box-folder 28:23)
    - York County (Box-folder 28:24)
    - Alexandria County (Box-folder 28:25)
    - Bristol City (Box-folder 28:26)
    - Clifton Forge (Box-folder 28:27)
    - Fredericksburg City (Box-folder 28:28)
    - Hampton City (Box-folder 28:29)
    - Harrisburg City (Box-folder 28:30)
    - Hopewell City (Box-folder 28:31)
    - Lynchburg City (Box-folder 28:32)
    - Norfolk City (Box-folder 28:33)
    - Radford City (Box-folder 28:34)
    - Staunton City (Box-folder 28:35)
    - Williamsburg City (Box-folder 28:36)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:37)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:38)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:39)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:40)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:41)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:42)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:43)
    - Maryland (Box-folder 28:44)
    - Manteo,N.C (Box-folder 28:45)
    - Winston Salem, N.C. (Box-folder 28:46)
    - (Box-folder 28:47)
    - Unknown (Box-folder 28:48)
- Scrapbooks and Yearbooks
  - Echo Yearbook 1962 (Othertype 29)
  - Pictorial History of Negro Education in Virginia (Othertype 29)
  - Retirement Book (Othertype 29)
  - Richardsonian Yearbook 1969 (Othertype 29)